<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FAE Space Pirates</title>
    <link>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/</link>
    <description>Recent content on FAE Space Pirates</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Russell Hay See License</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Starship</title>
      <link>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/rules/starship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/rules/starship/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;A starship is any vehical that is capable of interstellar travel.  Following
the Fate Fractal, a starship is defined by:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two Aspects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One Stunt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, a starship contains two stress tracks:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hull&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The exact number of boxes associated with each stress track depends on the
type of ship it is.  Additional stress tracks can be created for different
systems (e.g. shields, weapons, life support) if it is desired.
See Examples below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;weapon-systems:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Weapon Systems&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Weapon systems are one additional layer to a starship that needs to be
considered.  It can be assumed that all starships have a basic weapon system
which are forward-facing &amp;ldquo;asteroid-destroyers&amp;rdquo;, small wavelength, moderately
powerful lasers designed to, well, destroy asteroids.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In games that will focus heavily on ship-to-ship combat, a starship can have
two additional aspects to represent the weapons systems, otherwise, weapon
systems should be treated just like &amp;ldquo;extras&amp;rdquo; from Fate Core.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;example-weapon-system-aspects:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Example Weapon System Aspects&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;todo&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;crewing-the-ship:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Crewing The Ship&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each standing member of a starship should take an aspect that represents
their place on the starship.  This aspect will relate to their job on the
starship and what they contribute to the overall community of that starship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In many instances, only one character can be a certain role.  Here are the
roles that are unique on a starship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;captain:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Captain&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Commander of the ship who has ultimate authority over the goings on on the
ship.  This is usually the most charismatic person on the ship, but sometimes
the most feared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;quartermaster:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Quartermaster&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During combat, the Quartermaster is in charge.  They are the admiral at
arms, and are responsible for tactics in the heat of a battle.  While the
captain maintains ultimate authority, during a battle, the QM calls the shots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A quartermaster is usually only found on war ships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;starnav:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Starnav&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The starnav is responsible for navigation among the stars and wormholes that
exist in the world.  They are responsible for staying the course, and getting
the starship from location to location.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;boatswain:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Boatswain&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Boatswain is responsible for communication on the starship, across all
departments, and to effectively communicate the captain&amp;rsquo;s desires.  They
also tend to the supervision of less critical roles, like the galley, and
ensuring the starship stays clean.  They are usually the one who operates
communication devices for inter-ship communications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;chief-engineer:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Chief Engineer&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Chief Engineer is responsible for the maintanence of the starship, and
ensuring that all systems are functional and that the hull remains in good
repair.  A starship lives and dies by the integrity of it&amp;rsquo;s hull, and the
Chief Engineer is the master of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;master-gunner:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Master Gunner&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On war ships, the master gunner is in charge of the weapon and shield systems.
In the case of needed ammunition, the master gunner is also in charge of
keeping track of stock and informing the captain when more ammunition is
needed.  They also work with the Chief Engineer to ensure that everything
is kept in good working order.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;rigger:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Rigger&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Need something fixed that isn&amp;rsquo;t easily within reach?  The rigger&amp;rsquo;s got you
covered.  Their responsibilities include any EVA missions, as well as climbing
through any of the duct work.  If it&amp;rsquo;s high up, in the vacuum of space, or
requires a complicated set of pulleys and rope to get to, the rigger will
be who you&amp;rsquo;d call on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;other-roles:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Other roles&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like any ship, a starship will contain a host of able bodied sailors to help
with anything that needs to happen.  On certain ships, and with Captains who
fancy themselves more important than they really are, a cabin child might
be on board to act as their valet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;example-starships:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Example Starships&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;todo&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>