<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FAE Space Pirates</title>
    <link>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/</link>
    <description>Recent content on FAE Space Pirates</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Russell Hay See License</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Space</title>
      <link>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/world/space/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/world/space/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Space exists as it exists in the real world, however, the human race has managed to colonize Mars as
research station for longer term colonization.  Very few humans live outside of the orbit of Sol.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;mars-station:667829fb4acf3b47e2eb279490a07306&#34;&gt;Mars Station&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mars Station is a research facility for advanced colonization techniques.  Created by &lt;code&gt;Mars Unity&lt;/code&gt;, this facility is
a host to experiments for long term exoplanet colonization.  There are currently 10,000 researchers, engineers, and
volunteer colonizers living and working on a 100 year mission.  Escape vehicles and a orbiting, AI-controlled rescue
transport ship are their safety plan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;exoplanets:667829fb4acf3b47e2eb279490a07306&#34;&gt;Exoplanets&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;silorsa-major:667829fb4acf3b47e2eb279490a07306&#34;&gt;Silorsa Major&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Silorsa Major is the home world of the Fireon, a warmongering race of bipedal felines, who command a vast armada of
small, agile and deadly starships.  The planet itself is a lush, verdant world with large meadows, raging rivers.  It
contains a single land mass that is called Simta, and the vast ocean that surrounds Simta is called Winra.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Species</title>
      <link>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/world/species/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/world/species/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;The multitudes are infinite.  Higher life forms take all shapes and sizes.  If it can be imagined, it exists in the
universe.  A species of bipedal feline warriors from the planet Silorsa Major, sure why not?  Unless the species has something
extraordinary about them (e.g. thermal vision, subsonic hearing, etc.)  The species of a character in Space Pirate is
wide open.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the species has some extraordinary aspect to them, the characters of that species must take a stunt or aspect to back
up that extraordinary feature of the species, or come up with a narrative reason why no bonus is granted for having that
characteristic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See the &lt;a href=&#34;../characters&#34;&gt;NPC List&lt;/a&gt; to see examples of how a species with extraordinary characteristics can be made.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;known-species:b43f82befe7c5b419f90e0bb00677469&#34;&gt;Known Species&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-fireon:b43f82befe7c5b419f90e0bb00677469&#34;&gt;The Fireon&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fireon are bipedal felines.  They are rules by a council of seven elders, from the seven tribes of the Fireon.
The Fireon are skilled warriors, fierce and deadly should someone cross their path.  While skilled at starship combat,
they shine particularly at hand to hand fighting, preferring bladed weapons over any other kinds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their species contains three distinct genders called the Toreon, Lareon, and the Cireon.  Any combination of the two are
capable of producing offspring, but the species tends towards not pair-bonding, but tri-bonding. They have a ceremony
for bonding known as donta-fara-sheon, which involves sharing in each others blood.  The tri-bonding is permanent, for
life, but a Fireon is not expected to tri-bond.  When one member of the tri-bond dies, it is expected that the other
two Fireon will take part in the ritual of danto-fara-sheon, which is a form of ritual suicide to join their trimate
in the afterlife.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fireon have no codified religion, but they believe there is a world after death, and honor is the highest virtue.
When a Fireon has lost their honor, they are expected to shave all of their fur off, forsake all posessions, including
clothes, and live in the Fatala, a sandy expanse of land on the southern tip of Simta.  Fatala contains a temple from
 the ancient times, dedicated to some god that has long since forgotten.  The Fatala tradition of attonement for dishonor
 is the only vestiges of the religion.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starship</title>
      <link>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/world/starship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/world/starship/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;A starship is any vehical that is capable of interstellar travel.  Following
the Fate Fractal, a starship is defined by:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two Aspects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One Stunt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, a starship contains two stress tracks:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hull&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The exact number of boxes associated with each stress track depends on the
type of ship it is.  Additional stress tracks can be created for different
systems (e.g. shields, weapons, life support) if it is desired.
See Examples below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;weapon-systems:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Weapon Systems&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Weapon systems are one additional layer to a starship that needs to be
considered.  It can be assumed that all starships have a basic weapon system
which are forward-facing &amp;ldquo;asteroid-destroyers&amp;rdquo;, small wavelength, moderately
powerful lasers designed to, well, destroy asteroids.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In games that will focus heavily on ship-to-ship combat, a starship can have
two additional aspects to represent the weapons systems, otherwise, weapon
systems should be treated just like &amp;ldquo;extras&amp;rdquo; from Fate Core.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;example-weapon-system-aspects:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Example Weapon System Aspects&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;todo&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;crewing-the-ship:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Crewing The Ship&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each standing member of a starship should take an aspect that represents
their place on the starship.  This aspect will relate to their job on the
starship and what they contribute to the overall community of that starship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In many instances, only one character can be a certain role.  Here are the
roles that are unique on a starship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;captain:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Captain&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Commander of the ship who has ultimate authority over the goings on on the
ship.  This is usually the most charismatic person on the ship, but sometimes
the most feared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;quartermaster:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Quartermaster&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During combat, the Quartermaster is in charge.  They are the admiral at
arms, and are responsible for tactics in the heat of a battle.  While the
captain maintains ultimate authority, during a battle, the QM calls the shots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A quartermaster is usually only found on war ships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;starnav:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Starnav&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The starnav is responsible for navigation among the stars and wormholes that
exist in the world.  They are responsible for staying the course, and getting
the starship from location to location.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;boatswain:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Boatswain&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Boatswain is responsible for communication on the starship, across all
departments, and to effectively communicate the captain&amp;rsquo;s desires.  They
also tend to the supervision of less critical roles, like the galley, and
ensuring the starship stays clean.  They are usually the one who operates
communication devices for inter-ship communications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;chief-engineer:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Chief Engineer&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Chief Engineer is responsible for the maintanence of the starship, and
ensuring that all systems are functional and that the hull remains in good
repair.  A starship lives and dies by the integrity of it&amp;rsquo;s hull, and the
Chief Engineer is the master of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;master-gunner:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Master Gunner&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On war ships, the master gunner is in charge of the weapon and shield systems.
In the case of needed ammunition, the master gunner is also in charge of
keeping track of stock and informing the captain when more ammunition is
needed.  They also work with the Chief Engineer to ensure that everything
is kept in good working order.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;rigger:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Rigger&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Need something fixed that isn&amp;rsquo;t easily within reach?  The rigger&amp;rsquo;s got you
covered.  Their responsibilities include any EVA missions, as well as climbing
through any of the duct work.  If it&amp;rsquo;s high up, in the vacuum of space, or
requires a complicated set of pulleys and rope to get to, the rigger will
be who you&amp;rsquo;d call on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;other-roles:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Other roles&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like any ship, a starship will contain a host of able bodied sailors to help
with anything that needs to happen.  On certain ships, and with Captains who
fancy themselves more important than they really are, a cabin child might
be on board to act as their valet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;example-starships:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Example Starships&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;todo&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tema, Silorsa refugee</title>
      <link>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/characters/fulacala/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/characters/fulacala/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tema was born FulaCala. Like many of the Cireon, FulaCala is masculine in dress and
appearance, preferring short hair, simple, unadorned clothes, and no decorations on his collar. (When speaking
English, he prefers the masculine pronouns.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was born in the Fatala as a mating between FulaMa and FulaSima, an illegally pair-bonded Toreon and Lareon who
were turned in by their families for dishonor of the unnatural variety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon his birth, he was removed from the Fatala and became a ward of the council, where he was raised with strict
discipline and harsh punishments.  Upon his age day, the date when Fireons are granted 100% legal recognition as
an independent being, FulaCala decided to take a new name, Tema, and signed on as a sailor on the starship Ome, bound
for a distant settlement on the outer reaches of the star system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;../../charactersheets/tema.pdf&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;../../charactersheets/tema.png&#34; alt=&#34;Character Sheet&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>