<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FAE Space Pirates</title>
    <link>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/</link>
    <description>Recent content on FAE Space Pirates</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Russell Hay See License</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Ca&#39;hei Lan (KAH-hey-LAHN)</title>
      <link>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/world/species/caheilan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/world/species/caheilan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Ca’hei Lan are one of several genetically-modified species of human origin created by the Fac’ar - who have a
long history of kidnapping humans from Earth. Humans have long been seen as a viable species for genetic
experimentation, due to a relatively simple DNA structure, and their primitive status in the evolutionary chain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Early explorers sent to monitor Earth for harvesting noted that the human species had a predisposition towards sex and
violence. This was seen as a feature to be exploited, and the earliest Ca’hei Lan were designed to serve two purposes:
providing pleasure in the harems of Fac’ar nobles, and entertainment in the ‘gladiator rings’ of the Fac’ar government.
The species was bred on an outpost moon of the Fac’ar homeworld, with changes made to the human DNA structure that both
enhanced sexual drive, strength, and drive to attack when presented with a ‘fight or flight’ circumstance. This made
them into headstrong fighters and intense lovers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The major change to the human genetic sequence was the change to sex and gender. The Ca’hei Lan have no gender, but
are rather two-in-one: hermaphroditic, they present as so until puberty, at which time they gain the ability to change
from one gender to the other (taking on the traditional appearance and reproductive organs of the classic ‘female’
and ‘male’ genders of humans). They are technically both at once, but can ‘present’ as one or the other as they
choose; they accomplish this by moving bone structure and muscle/fat mass, much the way that an octopus might change
the color or texture of their skin. Each Ca’hei Lan has their own strength at making the change: for some it can be
instantaneous, and for others it can take up to several minutes. Additionally, not all Ca’hei Lan choose to switch
between the two ‘genders’; some prefer one form over the other, while others may change several times a day. The only
time they might switch back to their hermaphroditic ‘bi-gender’ appearance held before puberty is when sleeping or
unconscious; the ability to hold one of either form is a subconscious, not conscious, one - but sometimes a Ca’hei
Lan reverts when not fully conscious. Again, this can vary from Ca’hei Lan to Ca’hei Lan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aside from the change to gender and enhanced sexual drive and ‘attack mode’, there are almost no visible differences
between a Ca’hei Lan and a generic human. The few minor features that are present are a commonly androgynous look,
unusual eye colors (yellow, lavender, etc.), and the absence of body hair, other than on the top of the head
(meaning ‘male’ presenting Ca’hei Lan are incapable of growing facial hair).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ca’hei Lan have a culture created primarily around their existence as slaves and rebels of the Fac’ar state.
During the ages of breeding on the outpost moon, Ca’hei Lan were forbidden from mating or marrying their own kind;
they were seen as possessions, and could be bought and sold and separated at any time. This did not stop some of the
Ca’hei Lan from taking on secret lovers or mates, but resulted in a culture that placed no value on ‘marriage’.
Additionally, the lack of more than one ‘gender’ in the species resulted in an open-mindedness to mating and physical
forms. The Ca’hei Lan are a largely polysexual, polyamorous species, that prefer casual relationships or lovers to
monogamy or commitment; of course, there are those that break this mold, but almost all committed relationships
with a Ca’hei Lan occur when they are mated to a being of another species, and are always entirely based on the other
species’s views/culture/religion (having no cultural equivalent to ‘commitment’ or ‘marriage’ themselves).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nearly 2,000 years after the first Ca’hei Lan were bred, a resistance rose up on the outpost moon where the species was
primarily stationed before being sold off to various noble houses or the state. A war erupted, ending with the deaths
of nearly &lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;3&lt;/sub&gt; of all Ca’hei Lan on the moon; the rest killed their breeders and guardians, escaping on any vessels
available to them. The Ca’hei Lan became enemies of the Fac’ar state, and most are executed upon sight, even to this
day. Several members of the Fac’ar are more ambivalent about their one-time creations and slaves, and consider the
Ca’hei Lan pests and nothing more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to the lack of a homeworld, Ca’hei Lan are almost always born in space and many live their entire lives on
spaceships; this makes them extremely handy at navigation, piloting, and mechanics. Having a Ca’hei Lan on board is
considered somewhat lucky; they are rather rare in the galaxy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space</title>
      <link>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/world/space/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/world/space/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Space exists as it exists in the real world, however, the human race has managed to colonize Mars as
research station for longer term colonization.  Very few humans live outside of the orbit of Sol.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;mars-station:667829fb4acf3b47e2eb279490a07306&#34;&gt;Mars Station&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mars Station is a research facility for advanced colonization techniques.  Created by &lt;code&gt;Mars Unity&lt;/code&gt;, this facility is
a host to experiments for long term exoplanet colonization.  There are currently 10,000 researchers, engineers, and
volunteer colonizers living and working on a 100 year mission.  Escape vehicles and a orbiting, AI-controlled rescue
transport ship are their safety plan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;exoplanets:667829fb4acf3b47e2eb279490a07306&#34;&gt;Exoplanets&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;silorsa-major:667829fb4acf3b47e2eb279490a07306&#34;&gt;Silorsa Major&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Silorsa Major is the home world of the Fireon, a warmongering race of bipedal felines, who command a vast armada of
small, agile and deadly starships.  The planet itself is a lush, verdant world with large meadows, raging rivers.  It
contains a single land mass that is called Simta, and the vast ocean that surrounds Simta is called Winra.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Species</title>
      <link>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/world/species/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/world/species/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;The multitudes are infinite.  Higher life forms take all shapes and sizes.  If it can be imagined, it exists in the
universe.  A species of bipedal feline warriors from the planet Silorsa Major, sure why not?  Unless the species has something
extraordinary about them (e.g. thermal vision, subsonic hearing, etc.)  The species of a character in Space Pirate is
wide open.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the species has some extraordinary aspect to them, the characters of that species must take a stunt or aspect to back
up that extraordinary feature of the species, or come up with a narrative reason why no bonus is granted for having that
characteristic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See the &lt;a href=&#34;../characters&#34;&gt;NPC List&lt;/a&gt; to see examples of how a species with extraordinary characteristics can be made.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;known-species:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;Known Species&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;facar&#34;&gt;The Fac&amp;rsquo;ar&lt;/a&gt; - Purple-furred, giant Lemur-like creatures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;fireon&#34;&gt;The Fireon&lt;/a&gt; - a humanoid feline species&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;caheilan&#34;&gt;Ca&amp;rsquo;hei Lan&lt;/a&gt; - Genetically-modified human slave-species created by the Fac&amp;rsquo;ar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starship</title>
      <link>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/world/starship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/world/starship/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;A starship is any vehical that is capable of interstellar travel.  Following
the Fate Fractal, a starship is defined by:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two Aspects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One Stunt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, a starship contains two stress tracks:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hull&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The exact number of boxes associated with each stress track depends on the
type of ship it is.  Additional stress tracks can be created for different
systems (e.g. shields, weapons, life support) if it is desired.
See Examples below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;weapon-systems:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Weapon Systems&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Weapon systems are one additional layer to a starship that needs to be
considered.  It can be assumed that all starships have a basic weapon system
which are forward-facing &amp;ldquo;asteroid-destroyers&amp;rdquo;, small wavelength, moderately
powerful lasers designed to, well, destroy asteroids.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In games that will focus heavily on ship-to-ship combat, a starship can have
two additional aspects to represent the weapons systems, otherwise, weapon
systems should be treated just like &amp;ldquo;extras&amp;rdquo; from Fate Core.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;example-weapon-system-aspects:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Example Weapon System Aspects&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;todo&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;crewing-the-ship:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Crewing The Ship&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each standing member of a starship should take an aspect that represents
their place on the starship.  This aspect will relate to their job on the
starship and what they contribute to the overall community of that starship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In many instances, only one character can be a certain role.  Here are the
roles that are unique on a starship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;captain:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Captain&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Commander of the ship who has ultimate authority over the goings on on the
ship.  This is usually the most charismatic person on the ship, but sometimes
the most feared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;quartermaster:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Quartermaster&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During combat, the Quartermaster is in charge.  They are the admiral at
arms, and are responsible for tactics in the heat of a battle.  While the
captain maintains ultimate authority, during a battle, the QM calls the shots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A quartermaster is usually only found on war ships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;starnav:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Starnav&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The starnav is responsible for navigation among the stars and wormholes that
exist in the world.  They are responsible for staying the course, and getting
the starship from location to location.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;boatswain:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Boatswain&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Boatswain is responsible for communication on the starship, across all
departments, and to effectively communicate the captain&amp;rsquo;s desires.  They
also tend to the supervision of less critical roles, like the galley, and
ensuring the starship stays clean.  They are usually the one who operates
communication devices for inter-ship communications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;chief-engineer:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Chief Engineer&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Chief Engineer is responsible for the maintanence of the starship, and
ensuring that all systems are functional and that the hull remains in good
repair.  A starship lives and dies by the integrity of it&amp;rsquo;s hull, and the
Chief Engineer is the master of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;master-gunner:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Master Gunner&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On war ships, the master gunner is in charge of the weapon and shield systems.
In the case of needed ammunition, the master gunner is also in charge of
keeping track of stock and informing the captain when more ammunition is
needed.  They also work with the Chief Engineer to ensure that everything
is kept in good working order.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;rigger:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Rigger&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Need something fixed that isn&amp;rsquo;t easily within reach?  The rigger&amp;rsquo;s got you
covered.  Their responsibilities include any EVA missions, as well as climbing
through any of the duct work.  If it&amp;rsquo;s high up, in the vacuum of space, or
requires a complicated set of pulleys and rope to get to, the rigger will
be who you&amp;rsquo;d call on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;other-roles:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Other roles&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like any ship, a starship will contain a host of able bodied sailors to help
with anything that needs to happen.  On certain ships, and with Captains who
fancy themselves more important than they really are, a cabin child might
be on board to act as their valet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;example-starships:c63bfe9f5973b70c3ec26ce0239fa322&#34;&gt;Example Starships&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;todo&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sydney Daniels, AKA Starbaby</title>
      <link>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/characters/starbaby/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/characters/starbaby/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sydney Daniels was born in Iowa on a farm just outside of Des Moines.  Her family owned the farm until she was five, when
they had to sell it to a large commercial agriculture company.  They were allowed to continue to live on the farm and
work the fields, but the company was taking most of the profit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sydney was seven years old when the Fac&amp;rsquo;ar abducted her from her house. She was given as a present to the empress of the
Fac&amp;rsquo;ar, Gra&amp;rsquo;hera Lei, where she was treated as a servant girl until she was old enough to be trained as a member of the
Lian-Che, the royal assassins of the Fac&amp;rsquo;ar Empire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She quickly rose to through the ranks of the Lian-Che, becoming the personal bodyguard of Gra&amp;rsquo;hera Lei.  When the Fac&amp;rsquo;ar
declared war on the Walanti, and the Lian-Che were sent to rid the Walanti of their Magorice, Sydney remained behind
to protect Gra&amp;rsquo;hera Lei, but Sydney had other plans.  During the sleeping times, Sydney slipped into Gra&amp;rsquo;hera Lei&amp;rsquo;s
chambers, and ran her through with a dark blade, ending her life in the quiet of the night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, she stole a small transport ship and escaped the Fac&amp;rsquo;ar&amp;rsquo;s grasp, but she knows she isn&amp;rsquo;t safe.  She has taken the
moniker &amp;ldquo;Starbaby&amp;rdquo; in the hopes that the Fac&amp;rsquo;ar will not be able to trace her.  She ditched the ship on a small outpost
moon in the Silvanis System.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;../../charactersheets/starbaby.pdf&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;../../charactersheets/starbaby.png&#34; alt=&#34;Character Sheet&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tema, Silorsa refugee</title>
      <link>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/characters/fulacala/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/characters/fulacala/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tema was born FulaCala. Like many of the Cireon, FulaCala is masculine in dress and
appearance, preferring short hair, simple, unadorned clothes, and no decorations on his collar. (When speaking
English, he prefers the masculine pronouns.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was born in the Fatala as a mating between FulaMa and FulaSima, an illegally pair-bonded Toreon and Lareon who
were turned in by their families for dishonor of the unnatural variety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon his birth, he was removed from the Fatala and became a ward of the council, where he was raised with strict
discipline and harsh punishments.  Upon his age day, the date when Fireons are granted 100% legal recognition as
an independent being, FulaCala decided to take a new name, Tema, and signed on as a sailor on the starship Ome, bound
for a distant settlement on the outer reaches of the star system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;../../charactersheets/tema.pdf&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;../../charactersheets/tema.png&#34; alt=&#34;Character Sheet&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fac&#39;ar (fah&#39;CAR)</title>
      <link>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/world/species/facar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/world/species/facar/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Fac&amp;rsquo;ar are the most militant species in the entire known universe, and have a policy of colonize, assimilate,
decimate any planet that serves their purposes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The species is ancient, having existed for 10,000 years.  About 5000 years ago, they achieved inter-stellar technology
and began to explore and colonize nearby star systems.  They all but abandoned their original home world and settled a
larger planet, named Fac&amp;rsquo;ar Major, and covered every inch of the planet with Fac&amp;rsquo;arian technology. Fac&amp;rsquo;ar Major contains a sun that only emits ultraviolet light, though they can adjust to visible wavelengths, but only
on that range of the color spectrum.  They cannot see light in wavelengths shorter than blue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fac&amp;rsquo;ar believe they are the chosen people of the Rastraga (rah-STRAH-ga), their supreme diety, a faceless bird like
creature with large razor sharp feathers.  As such, they believe they rule, above all, with absolute agency in the name
of Rastraga.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fac&amp;rsquo;ar are a matriarchy, with an Empress as the embodiment of Rastraga, who channels and speaks as Rastraga.  They
believe that Rastraga possess the Empress when she is in her trance of channeling.  In reality, the trance is brought on
by a paralytic hallucinogen that is contained in the sacred tea that is consumed during religion rituals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fac&amp;rsquo;ar, as rightful &amp;ldquo;stewards&amp;rdquo; of the universe, enslave numerous species across the universe.  Humans were discovered
by the Fac&amp;rsquo;ar early in their history, and the Empress, Mak&amp;rsquo;Hera Wan, decreed that Earth would be left intact as a
supervised breeding colony.  Mak&amp;rsquo;Hera Wan studied the humans&amp;rsquo; lust for violence, and decided they would be harvested
as faithful assassins and trained warriors of the Lian-Che.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fac&amp;rsquo;ar are giant lemur-like creatures that average about 7 feet in height, and are covered in purple fur, though
the fur absorbs light of other wavelengths and retransmits them back in the purple and ultraviolet wavelengths, so
they always appear to glow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mating for the Fac&amp;rsquo;ar is a detailed and complex ritual of religious rights, chanting, and blood sacrifice (their own).
Because of this, the Fac&amp;rsquo;ar rarely mate with other Fac&amp;rsquo;ar.  Given the nature of their mating, they have developed cloning
and gene manipulation technology that allows them to create offspring in the lab, but every Fac&amp;rsquo;ar is expected to produce
at least one offspring through natural means once they come of age.  They will, however, engage in sex with other species
purely for pleasure, and have large prostitution trade on one of the minor outer moons of Fac&amp;rsquo;ar Major.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because the Fac&amp;rsquo;ar live for hundreds of years, they do not reach the age of maturity until they have surpassed 100 years
according to the calendar on Fac&amp;rsquo;ar Major, which is equivalent to 0.97 earth-years.  Before their 100th year, they are
not allowed to perform the mating ritual, nor are they allowed to be cell donors for the cloning and gene manipulation
process.  They are not forbidden to partake in any other activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fac&amp;rsquo;arian empire is in a state of turmoil as the Empress, Gre&amp;rsquo;Hera Lei, was assassinated by a rogue member of the
Lian-Che, who escaped before being brought to justice.  The Dan&amp;rsquo;sto, the royal scientists, are working around the clock
to regenerated Lei before Rastraga is lost forever.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fireon (FE-re-OWN)</title>
      <link>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/world/species/fireon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poorimpulse.github.io/fae-spacepirate/world/species/fireon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Fireon are bipedal felines.  They are rules by a council of seven elders, from the seven tribes of the Fireon.
The Fireon are skilled warriors, fierce and deadly should someone cross their path.  While skilled at starship combat,
they shine particularly at hand to hand fighting, preferring bladed weapons over any other kinds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their species contains three distinct genders called the Toreon (TO-re-OWN), Lareon (LA-re-OWN), and the Cireon (KEY-re-OWN).  Any combination of the two are
capable of producing offspring, but the species tends towards not pair-bonding, but tri-bonding. They have a ceremony
for bonding known as donta-fara-sheon (DON-toe FAH-rah SHE-own), which involves sharing in each others blood.  The tri-bonding is permanent, for
life, but a Fireon is not expected to tri-bond.  When one member of the tri-bond dies, it is expected that the other
two Fireon will take part in the ritual of danto-fara-sheon, which is a form of ritual suicide to join their trimate
in the afterlife.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fireon have no codified religion, but they believe there is a world after death, and honor is the highest virtue.
When a Fireon has lost their honor, they are expected to shave all of their fur off, forsake all possessions, including
clothes, and live in the Fatala (FAH&amp;rsquo;tah-lah), a sandy expanse of land on the southern tip of Simta (SIM-ta).  Fatala contains a temple from
 the ancient times, dedicated to some god that has long since forgotten.  The Fatala tradition of atonement for dishonor
 is the only vestiges of the religion.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>